Hasnain Raza

MERN Stack developer

Github: https://github.com/hasnainraza1212

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hasnain-mern-developer

Portfolio: https://hasnain-mern.netlify.app/

Email: hasnaindeveloper786@gmail.com

BACKGROUND

Goal-oriented passionate website-Developer and solutions-oriented problem-solver. Use numerous website design software systems to develop customer-focused websites web design. Committed to high standards of website design, user experience, usability, and speed for multiple forms of end-users. Fortunate in maintaining client satisfaction.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, Bootstrap, Redux, Material-UI, Formik, React Redux, Ant Design, React Query, Tailwind CSS, Lodash, Redux Persist and Socket.IO.

MongoDB, Express, Node.js, Socket.lO, Firebase, Helmet, Passport, Mongoose, Redis, Morgan, Bcrypt, Joi, Sequelize, Multer, Nodemailer and JWT.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MarkCoders Jan-2024 - Present

Front-End Developer

- Made Responsive provided websites using the latest technology such as React, Redux and Material-UI with API connectivity.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Created an eye catching and cross-platform Web Application.
- Backend server on Nodejs
- Closely work with the Business and QA team so we can deploy the best product.
- Front-end Architecture and State management using Redux

NOP-Commerce Jan 2022 - Jan 2024

Front-End Developer

- Made Responsive website using the latest technology such as React, Redux and React-Bootstrap.
- Built a chat system based on firebase.
- Built multiple dashboards on latest Tech-stack.
- Experienced in converting and adding features to a prebuilt admin panel in Angular and React JS.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Graduation

2020-Present

BSCS student at FUUAST.

Intermediate

2018-2020

Completed intermediate from PECHS.

Schooling

2016-2018

Hassan Academy

RECENT PROJECTS

Linton Communication System

Developed a project management tool to streamline tasks, progress tracking, and resource allocation. Visit tool. <u>Vist tool</u>

Sauced App

Created a social media platform for culinary enthusiasts to discover, share, and review sauces, promoting community engagement.

App Store | Play Store